





Last Active: 20-Jan-21

1 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Experience in Tech-Functional and Database Oriented Software Development Using ASP.NET, C#.NET, VB.NET, Ajax, JQuery, WCF, Angular JS, Angula6, SQL SERVER 2008R2, SQL SERVER 2012. I have good Experience in Development, Coding, support & implementation of Software applications. Familiar with large operating environment, database management, System Interacted Application Development. Analytical thinker, consistently resolving ongoing issues. Successful track record in developing, implementing various projects within agreed cost/timelines without incidences of overruns.

Work Experience

- Liquidhub Analytics India (P) Ltd., (Capgemini Group Company) as Sr. Consultant -Dot Net Feb 2012 to Aug 2020
- LiquidHub as Senior Consultant Feb 2012 to Till Date

My Roles and Responsibilities in the organizations are :

?Production Support, Project Delivery & Client coordination, Requirement gathering Team handling, Creating FRD's, PSD for the requirement, Task allocation to team, Development, Code Review, Release Management

B2C Systems Ltd. as SSE May 2007 to Feb 2012

?Coding, development with SQL Server (Stored Procedure, Functions, Views, Triggers), Deploying application on Client Server, Client Support

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from Vinoba Bhave University (VBU) in 2001
PG: MCA (Computers) from Uttar Pradesh Technical University (UPTU) in 2005

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
C#.Net, VB.Net			
Python			
MS SQL SERVER 2000			
PLSQL, Stored Procedure			
MS-ACCESS, MYSQL			
ASP.NET, Ajax, Jquery			
JavaScript, AngularJS, Angular 6			
CRYSTAL REPORT9			
IIS 6.0, IIS 7.5			
DCOM, SMS Services, openXML			
VSTFS 2010			
Microsoft Azure, Azure Devops			
Windows98/2000 Server/Pro/XP2/2003 Serve			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak	
English					
Hindi					

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.